http://www.hubert.com/content/privacy_and_security

New Products
Last Chance Clearance!
New Products
Last Chance Clearance!
My Orders
Feedback?
Feedback?
We care a lot about your experience on our website. Please tell
us how we can improve.
Feedback Reason:
Select Reason
Problem with product
Problem with website
Other feedback
Email: (optional)
Feedback:
Privacy Policy
The Hubert.com Web site is maintained by the Hubert Company, LLC. Our address is 9555 Dry Fork Road, Harrison, OH 45030. Our data collection and use policies with respect to the site are set forth in this statement. By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.
Hubert is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (the phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our Web site, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information. This policy applies only to users accessing our Web site from the United States.
As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Hubert Distribution supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise" and the Canadian Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL). Hubert never sells, rents or shares your e-mail address.
Collecting Information About You
In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics. We use information collected on the site to evaluate how the site is being used. For example, we may collect and analyze information about how many visitors went to certain pages, how long they stayed at those pages and where they went afterwards. This information allows us to determine which pages are popular and enables us to provide visitors with a more enriching experience on our website. However, individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.
There may be times when you order a product, subscribe to a service, register to receive catalogs, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, purchase order number, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. We also maintain a record of your online product purchases. Whether or not you provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our website.
Using Information About You
We use the personally identifiable information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services, and offers, etc.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online or offline, including search and shopping behavior. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, and to communicate with you by phone, email or physical mail about our products and events that may be of interest to you.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Hubert or to others. Hubert may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it.
Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us via email, please let us know by calling 1.800.543.7374 in the U.S. or 1.888.835.7929 in Canada or by sending an email. Please be sure to include your email address and full name. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street address or other personal information with us, please contact us the same way.
Because we need to update our records, sometimes these requests may take up to 30 days to be effective. In addition, when you purchase from us online or through our catalogs we may need to contact you via email to address questions specific to your order, even if you have opted to not receive communications.
Please remember, if you delete certain information you may not be able to continue to purchase products or access other portions of our Web site without entering additional information.
Spam
Hubert never sells, rents or shares your email address. Nor do we buy or rent e-mail lists from other sources. We are very concerned about the growth of spam email messages, and we know that you are, too. We believe that spam jeopardizes the right of legitimate companies to conduct business electronically, both now and in the future. The purpose of our email messages is to provide you with ideas or offers that will help you conduct business more successfully. Our emails are designed to be timely, targeted and interesting.
You will only receive a Commercial Electronic Message (CEM) from Hubert if you have opted-in to receive them, or have done business with us within the past 24 months. That has been our policy long before CASL came into effect. You always have the option to opt-out of these. A link is included in all of our CEM messages to allow you to easily opt-out. Your opt-out will be implemented the next business day.
Many of our customers appreciate getting e-mail confirmations of their orders and tracking links, surveys to provide their feedback, and invoices. These are not CEMs. CEMs are promotional in nature. Opting out of CEMs will not prevent you from getting business transaction e-mails from us.
Cookies
Our website uses "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyzing your visiting patterns. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.
Security
We use sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our website, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems.
Also remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our website may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. We attempt to link to sites who share our business ethics. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.
Policy Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our Web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our Web site and will replace any prior policies which are inconsistent.
Your Feedback
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may email us or write to us at
Hubert
Attn: Marketing Dept
9555 Dry Fork Road
Harrison, OH 45030-1994.
Mailto:marketing@hubert.com
We Are Here To Help You
If you have any questions, please use any one of the ways below to get in touch with us. Thank You
Chat with us
Mon – Fri 8am – 6pm ET
Email Us
Your Questions or Comments.
Toll Free 1.877.276.7773
Mon – Fri 7:30am – 6:30pm ET
Shipping
Shipping Methods Shipping Time Guarantee
About Us
Quick Order Form
Merchandising Solutions
Visit CCM
Free Merchandising Services Catalog Resource Center Request Catalog Contact Us About Us
Information
FAQs Special Order Services Subscribe to Email Supplier Connection Privacy and Security Employment Opportunities Site Map Download W9 Form Credit Application
Shipping
Shipping Methods Shipping Time Guarantee
About Us
Quick Order Form
Catalog Resource Center Request Free Catalog Contact Us About Us
Additional information
FAQs Special Order Services Supplier Connection Privacy and Security Employment Opportunities Site Map Download W9 Form Credit Application
Your email address is added to our list.
Delivery days are shown in the number of business days.
Close
×
SIGN UP NOW!
Be the first to receive:
